{
    "id": "125b89de52734a5f91a81dd0a52b6615",
    "title": "Sequence Of Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You will find Coca-Cola wherever you ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "would go"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "03857117eeca4b7095f81473bd037d9a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He would never do anything that ………………… .. against his conscience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "goes",
                "went",
                "will go"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3137fd885bc141eab8df3fccf60232f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will lend it to you on condition that you ……………………… it back tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bring",
                "would bring",
                "brought"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "52568ad7e04d4dccbcdf3c6e06ce7102"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… a good time whether I win or lose.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "will have"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "436f74f031494009b84534e20e73ee4e"
        },
        {
            "question": "One day the government will ask people what they ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "will want",
                "wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "313f4544b58548fc8e9d9db1f920bde9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know where she …………………. tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "will be",
                "would be"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2701c6d08ad1492e9b19aca9a0dce8b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had lots of money, I would give some to anybody who ………………… for it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ask",
                "asks",
                "asked"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b1c540fa143d4db6b0619fd85763cf91"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have brought my tennis things, just in case we ………………… time for a game tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "will have",
                "would have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8212d4a2b51941deba41bfdc4f8f5598"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will go where you …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "will go",
                "would go"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9e15ccb3567f4f7ab1efd184726707db"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will tell you when I …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finished",
                "have finished",
                "had finished"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ff09a924d59b426db00009589a57f3b9"
        }
    ]
}